{
    "subject": "resource/Irma_Elsa_Gonzalez",
    "predicate": "property/office",
    "object": "Chief Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of California",
    "human_readable": "Irma Elsa Gonzalez was the Chief Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9788697361946106,
            "question": "For which court was Irma Elsa Gonzalez the Chief Judge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8780227899551392,
            "question": "Who was Irma Elsa Gonzalez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7608397006988525,
            "question": "What type of court was the Southern District of California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5811782479286194,
            "question": "What position did Irma Elsa Gonzalez hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5411179661750793,
            "question": "Can you name a significant legal case that Irma Elsa Gonzalez might have presided over?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3694309592247009,
            "question": "In what part of California was the court located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2603979706764221,
            "question": "How does the role of a Chief Judge differ from other judges?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2034340500831604,
            "question": "What are some qualities that might be important for a Chief Judge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0564718097448349,
            "question": "What are some challenges that judges might face in their work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.036125387996435165,
            "question": "What is the importance of an impartial judicial system?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Irma Elsa Gonzalez was the Chief Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1423_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges that judges might face in their work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1423_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some qualities that might be important for a Chief Judge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1423_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the role of a Chief Judge differ from other judges?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1423_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1423_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate the triple as follows:\n\n**Triple:** Irma Elsa Gonzalez was the Chief Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of California.\n\n**Evaluation:**\n\nThe context information mentions that Judge Irma Gonzalez served as Chief Judge of the District Court from January 2005 to January 2012. This information supports the triple, indicating that the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Irma E. Gonzalez served as Chief Judge of the District Court from January, 2005 to January, 2012, which supports the statement that she was the Chief Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of California."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}